Guide to the C-SPAN records, 1809, 1978-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Series 8: Executive Files and Correspondence (Boxes 229-402), 1976-2009
  - Professors' Seminars, 1991-1992 (Box 351, Folder 6)
  - Short Subject, 1991-1992 (Box 351, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN Viewing Statistics, 1991-1993 (Box 351, Folder 8)
  - Ads, 1989-1992 (Box 351, Folder 9)
  - Courts, 1990 (Box 351, Folder 10)
  - Programming, 1981-1992 (Box 351, Folder 11)
  - Travel Documents, 1990 (Box 351, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 351, Folder 13)
  - Call-in, 1990-1991 (Box 351, Folder 14)
  - Presidential Campaign 1992, 1988-1992 (Box 351, Folder 15)
  - Specials, 1991 (Box 351, Folder 16)
  - Pool Feeds, 1990-1991 (Box 351, Folder 17)
  - Program Statistics, 1991-1992 (Box 351, Folder 18)
  - Education Documents, 1991-1992 (Box 351, Folder 19)
  - Cable Clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 352, Folder 1)
  - Promotions/Reports, 1991 (Box 352, Folder 2)
  - Viewer, 1990-1992 (Box 352, Folder 3)
  - Viewer Mail, 1991-1992 (Box 352, Folder 4)
  - Marketing, 1991-1993 (Box 352, Folder 5)
  - Articles and America 2000 Pamphlet, 1992 (Box 352, Folder 6)
  - Marketing #5, 1991-1992 (Box 352, Folder 7)
  - TCI, 1991-1992 (Box 352, Folder 8)
  - C-SPAN Hosted Events, 1991 (Box 352, Folder 9)
  - C-SPAN Capital Report, 1989-1991 (Box 352, Folder 10)
  - Info on Specific Geographical Areas, 1991 (Box 352, Folder 11)
  - Part-time Carriage, 1991 (Box 352, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence-Preemptions, 1991 (Box 352, Folder 13)
  - Cable Co. Facts-Board Member [Illegible], 1991 (Box 352, Folder 14)
  - Contracts, 1991-1989 (Box 352, Folder 15)
  - Survey Data, 1991 (Box 352, Folder 16)
  - C-SPAN and C-SPAN2-Second Quarter-Affiliate Marketing Report-Fiscal Year 1992, September 30, 1991 (Box 352, Folder 17)
  - June 1988 Board Meeting and Dinner-Jefferson Hotel, 1986-1988 (Box 352, Folder 18)
  - June 1988 Board Meeting and Dinner-The Folger Shakespeare Library, 1987-1988 (Box 352, Folder 19)
  - June 1988 Board Meeting and Dinner (Box 352, Folder 20)
  - June 1988 Board Meeting and Dinner-C-SPAN Board of Directors Meeting-The Capital Hilton (Box 353, Folder 1)
  - June 1988 Board Meeting and Dinner (Box 353, Folder 2)
  - June 1988 Board Meeting and Dinner-Tina Chauncey (Box 353, Folder 3)
  - June 1988 Board Meeting and Dinner-Documents for June, 1988 Board Book, 1987-1989 (Box 353, Folder 4)
  - June 1988 Board Meeting and Dinner, 1987-1988 (Box 353, Folder 5)
  - June 1988 Board Meeting and Dinner-Design Cuisine-Caterers (Box 353, Folder 6)
  - C-SPAN Board of Directors Meeting-Anaheim, CA, December 8, 1988 (Box 353, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN Executive Committee Meeting-New York, September 28, 1988 (Box 353, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, September 27, 1989 (Box 353, Folder 9)
  - C-SPAN Executive Committee Meeting-New York, September 25, 1990 (Box 353, Folder 10)
  - C-SPAN Executive Committee Meeting-New York-Originals For Board Book, September 25, 1990 (Box 353, Folder 11)
  - C-SPAN Board of Directors Meeting-Washington, DC, April 24, 1990 (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN Board of Directors Meeting-Washington, DC, March-April 1990 (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN Board of Directors Meeting-Washington, DC, April 24, 1990 (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Kevin Phillips-The American Political Report, March 1990 (Box 354, Folder 4)
  - C-SPAN Board of Directors Meeting-Washington, DC, March-April 1990 (Box 354, Folder 5)
  - Printed Images-Bill Wise, March-April 1990 (Box 354, Folder 6)
  - Notes from Meetings; Lists of Things to Do; Timeline, February 1990 (Box 354, Folder 7)
  - Ritz Carlton-Guest Rooms and Dinner Arrangements, March-April 1990 (Box 354, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors-Notes, Correspondence, RSVPs, December 1989-February 1990 (Box 354, Folder 9)
  - The Capitol, January 2, 1990 (Box 354, Folder 10)
  - Audio/Visual, February-April 1990 (Box 354, Folder 11)
  - Budget, April 24, 1990 (Box 354, Folder 12)
  - Original Board Book Documents, April 1989-April 1990 (Box 354, Folder 13)
  - Ritz Carlton, March-April 1990 (Box 354, Folder 14)
  - Budget Car Rental, February 23, 1990 (Box 354, Folder 15)
  - State Services-Meeting Rooms 239 and 237, September 1989-April 1990 (Box 354, Folder 16)
  - C-SPAN 2000/LTF 93D, 2003 (Box 354, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee Presentation, circa 1993 (Box 354, Folder 18)
  - C-SPAN 2000 Financial Plan-Early, 1992 (Box 354, Folder 19)
  - LTF 93E-C-SPAN Memorandum, May 1993 (Box 354, Folder 20)
  - VI Financial Protections, 1993 (Box 355, Folder 1)
  - Budget Documents, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Fees-C-SPAN 2000, 1992 (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Financial Studies, March-June 1993 (Box 355, Folder 4)
  - Supporting Documents, June 1993 (Box 355, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, Spring 1993 (Box 355, Folder 6)
  - Board Meeting Agenda, June 1992 (Box 355, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, Fall 1991 (Box 355, Folder 8)
  - Carriage Challenges, May 1991 (Box 355, Folder 9)
  - Membership, 1988-1989 (Box 355, Folder 10)
  - PPM-Material Produced by C-SPAN, 1991 (Box 355, Folder 11)
  - Due Diligence Meeting, April 30, 1991 (Box 355, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee Resolution, May 1991 (Box 355, Folder 13)
  - Internal Correspondence, February 13-14, 1991 (Box 355, Folder 14)
  - Board Resolution, July 1990-May 1991 (Box 355, Folder 15)
  - Ferris Baker Watts Documents, 1990-1991 (Box 355, Folder 16)
  - USAA, 1992 (Box 355, Folder 17)
  - Debt Service Analyses, 1990 (Box 355, Folder 18)
  - S and P Rating Letter, 1991 (Box 355, Folder 19)
  - Term/Structure, 1991 (Box 355, Folder 20)
  - Satellite Financing Summary, 1991 (Box 355, Folder 21)
  - Facility/Cap Interest Funds, 1991 (Box 355, Folder 22)
  - Requisitions, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 23)
  - Satellite Principal Payment, 1992-1993 (Box 355, Folder 24)
  - Cap Interest-Ongoing, 1991-1993 (Box 356, Folder 1)
  - Trustee, 1991 (Box 356, Folder 2)
  - Republican Convention, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 3)
  - 92 Conventions-Technical, circa 1990 (Box 356, Folder 4)
  - Jesse Jackson DNC Speech Article, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 5)
  - Kelo Land TV Documents, circa 1990 (Box 356, Folder 6)
  - 1992 Election, 1991-1992 (Box 356, Folder 7)
  - Network Pool, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 8)
  - Conventions 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 356, Folder 9)
  - Democratic Convention-Staffing, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 10)
  - Mock Election, C-SPAN 2000, and Democratic National Convention Documents, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 11)
  - C-SPAN 2000-Board Lunches, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 12)
  - Rob Kennedy-C-SPAN 2000 Education Outreach, April 1, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 13)
  - Customer Relations, May 16, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 14)
  - Compression, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 15)
  - Financial Planning, 1991-1992 (Box 356, Folder 16)
  - Memorandum, March 16, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 17)
  - C-SPAN 2000-Alternative Dist./Revenue, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 18)
  - C-SPAN 2000-General, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 19)
  - C-SPAN 2000/John Evans/Group Meetings, circa 1992 (Box 356, Folder 20)
  - C-SPAN 2000/Board Book, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 21)
  - Organizational Impact, April 2, 1992 (Box 356, Folder 22)
  - Composition Book-FY 95-Planning, 1995 (Box 356, Folder 23)
  - FY 95 Revenue, March 24, 1994 (Box 356, Folder 24)
  - FY 95 Roll Ups, January 18, 1994 (Box 356, Folder 25)
  - Long Term Forecasts-FY 95, 1993 (Box 356, Folder 26)
  - FY 95 Budget-Set Up, 1993 (Box 356, Folder 27)
  - FY 95 Allocations, April and July 1994 (Box 356, Folder 28)
  - FY 95 and Benefits, 1994 (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - FY 94 Budget Documents, 1992-1993 (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - FY 94 Budget Documents, 1992 (Box 357, Folder 3)
  - Marketing FY 94 Documents, 1992-1994 (Box 357, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Engineering '94, 1992 (Box 357, Folder 5)
  - Corporate Budget Items, 1993-1994 (Box 357, Folder 6)
  - FY 1993 and 1994 Budget Documents, 1992-1994 (Box 357, Folder 7)
  - FY 94 Budget Documents, 1993 (Box 357, Folder 8)
  - Marketing-FY 94 Budget Documents, 1993 (Box 357, Folder 9)
  - Audited Financials-Distribution, 1990-1991 (Box 357, Folder 10)
  - Fairfax County Economic Development Authority and National Cable Satellite Corporation, May 1, 1991 (Box 357, Folder 11)
  - Trust Indenture Between Fairfax County Economic Development Authority and US Trust Company of New York-Revenue Bonds, May 1, 1991 (Box 357, Folder 12)
  - Arbitrage, June 21, 1991 (Box 357, Folder 13)
  - C-SPAN Forecast, 1990 (Box 357, Folder 14)
  - Standard and Poor's Ratings Group Document, 1990-1991 (Box 357, Folder 15)
  - C-SPAN 2000 Strategic Overview, 1993 (Box 357, Folder 16)
  - C-SPAN 2000 Documents, circa 1994 (Box 358, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN 2000: Outline-Environmental Changes, circa 1994 (Box 358, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN: An Assessment-Strengths and Weaknesses, circa 1994 (Box 358, Folder 3)
  - C-SPAN and C-SPAN2: The Core Product, 1993 (Box 358, Folder 4)
  - Communications-FY94, 1994 (Box 358, Folder 5)
  - Budget Information, September 16, 1993 (Box 358, Folder 6)
  - International Distribution, circa 1993 (Box 358, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN 2000: Carriage Projections, March 1993 (Box 358, Folder 8)
  - Competitive Analysis, 1993 (Box 358, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Issue, 1991 (Box 358, Folder 10)
  - General Calculations, 1989-1993 (Box 358, Folder 11)
  - Composition Book-"Bond Research,", circa 1993 (Box 358, Folder 12)
  - Expenses, 1991-1993 (Box 358, Folder 13)
  - Institutional Trading Corporation, 1990 (Box 358, Folder 14)
  - Distribution Lists, 1991 (Box 358, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1989-1990 (Box 358, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, April-May 1991 (Box 358, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, June 1991 (Box 358, Folder 18)
  - Legal Feasibility, 1990-1991 (Box 358, Folder 19)
  - US West/FSA, December 10, 1990 (Box 358, Folder 20)
  - Document Review-First Draft, April 26, 1991 (Box 358, Folder 21)
  - The Sumitomo Trust Documents, January-February 1991 (Box 358, Folder 22)
  - Failures and Letter of Credit Documents, May-June 1991 (Box 358, Folder 23)
  - Closing Documents, June 6, 13, 1991 (Box 358, Folder 24)
  - Update Publishing-General, 1991-1992 (Box 358, Folder 25)
  - FY 92 Budget-Update, 1991-1992 (Box 358, Folder 26)
  - Weekly UPO Meetings-FY 91, 1990-1991 (Box 359, Folder 1)
  - Convention Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 359, Folder 2)
  - Election '88, 1988 (Box 359, Folder 3)
  - Tier I and Tier II Election Committees, August 25, December 18, 1987 (Box 359, Folder 4)
  - New Orleans Hotel Project Documents, 1988 (Box 359, Folder 5)
  - Budget 1994 (Box 359, Folder 6)
  - Travel Budget, December 15, 1992 (Box 359, Folder 7)
  - Staff Costs, February-March 1993 (Box 359, Folder 8)
  - FY 94 Budget-Roll Up, 1993-1994 (Box 359, Folder 9)
  - Headcount and Initiatives, 1993 (Box 359, Folder 10)
  - Initial Roll Ups and Initiatives, 1994 (Box 359, Folder 11)
  - Budget Documents, 1994-1995 (Box 359, Folder 12)
  - Progress Reports 1988 Annual Fund, 1988-1989 (Box 359, Folder 13)
  - Composition Book and FY 94 Budget-C-SPAN 2000 Financial Detail Documents, 1993 (Box 359, Folder 14)
  - C-SPAN Long Term Forecast Documents, 1991-1994 (Box 360, Folder 1)
  - 91 Financial Plan/FY 93 Budget, 1991 (Box 360, Folder 2)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Correspondence-Part 1, 2007 (Box 360, Folder 3)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Correspondence-Part 2-Includes NBC Nightly News Segment on DVD, 2007 (Box 360, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Correspondence-Part 3, 2007 (Box 360, Folder 5)
  - Lamb Awards Correspondence-Includes DVD of Al Neuharth Award for Excellence in the Media, 1990s-2000s (Box 360, Folder 6)
  - United States Senate Youth Program and Correspondence, June 24, 2011 (Box 360, Folder 7)
  - Lone Sailor Awards Dinner, September 22, 2011 (Box 360, Folder 8)
  - C-SPAN's Emmy Award Photo Book, September 13, 2004 (Box 361, Folder 1)
  - The Media Institute Documents, August-September 2003 (Box 361, Folder 2)
  - Al Neuharth Award Documents, October 5-7, 2011 (Box 361, Folder 3)
  - Gaylord Prize Documents, November 6-8, 2011 (Box 361, Folder 4)
  - Giants of Broadcasting Luncheon Documents, October 14, 2011 (Box 361, Folder 5)
  - Awards to Lamb and C-SPAN-Includes Congratulatory Letter from George W. Bush, 2000s (Box 361, Folder 6)
  - Literacy in Media Awards Documents, 2002 (Box 361, Folder 7)
  - George Foster Peabody Awards Documents, 2000 (Box 361, Folder 8)
  - NPC Award Documents, 2002 (Box 361, Folder 9)
  - C-SPAN: America's Town Hall-Part 1, circa 1988 (Box 361, Folder 10)
  - C-SPAN: America's Town Hall-Part 2, circa 1988 (Box 361, Folder 11)
  - C-SPAN: America's Town Hall-Part 3, circa 1988 (Box 361, Folder 12)
  - The C-SPAN Update Survey, September 1987 (Box 362, Folder 1)
  - Donor Spot Log, 1987-1989 (Box 362, Folder 2)
  - 1988 Annual Fund Corporate Campaign-Part 1 (Box 362, Folder 3)
  - 1988 Annual Fund Corporate Campaign-Part 2 (Box 362, Folder 4)
  - Tocqueville Documents, 1996-1997 (Box 362, Folder 5)
  - The C-SPAN School Bus Tocqueville Tour, 1997 (Box 362, Folder 6)
  - Tocqueville Tour Documents-Part 1, 1997 (Box 363, Folder 1)
  - Tocqueville Tour Documents-Part 2, 1997 (Box 363, Folder 2)
  - Tocqueville Tour Documents-Part 3, 1997 (Box 363, Folder 3)
  - France Trip-Splaine's Notes, August 1997 (Box 363, Folder 4)
  - Tocqueville Tour Photos, August 1997 (Box 363, Folder 5)
  - Culvercatures Cartoons, 1997 (Box 363, Folder 6)
  - Tocqueville Tour-France Documents, April 1997 (Box 363, Folder 7)
  - Press Clippings from C-SPAN's Alexis de Tocqueville Tour, May 1997-January 1998 (Box 364, Folder 1)
  - Journey to America-Tocqueville and Beaumont By George Wilson Pierson-A Compilation, circa 1997 (Box 364, Folder 2)
  - Contemporary Tocqueville References (The Short List), circa 1997 (Box 364, Folder 3)
  - Tocqueville Tour Documents, 1997 (Box 364, Folder 4)
  - Tocqueville Tour Documents, 1997 (Box 364, Folder 5)
  - Tocqueville Tour News Release, March 21, 1997 (Box 365, Folder 1)
  - Tocqueville Tour Documents, 1997 (Box 365, Folder 2)
  - Tocqueville Tour Documents, 1997 (Box 365, Folder 3)
  - Booknotes-Life Stories Documents, 1998 (Box 365, Folder 4)
  - 25th Anniversary Dinner Correspondence, November 7, 2003 (Box 365, Folder 5)
  - 20th Anniversary Project Ideas, 1999 (Box 365, Folder 6)
  - 20th Anniversary Exhibit, 1999 (Box 365, Folder 7)
  - 20th Anniversary Dinner Documents, 1999 (Box 365, Folder 8)
  - Board Meeting Agenda Overview, March 25, 1999 (Box 365, Folder 9)
  - Board Meeting Attendance and Hotel Arrangements, 1999 (Box 365, Folder 10)
  - Dinner Committee, 1999 (Box 365, Folder 11)
  - Trivia/Dinner Program-Other Printing/Vendors (Margaret), 1999 (Box 365, Folder 12)
  - Speakers-Including David McCullough, 1999 (Box 365, Folder 13)
  - 20th Anniversary Dinner-Creative Services, 1999 (Box 366, Folder 1)
  - 20th Anniversary Dinner-Communication/Staff Awareness, 1999 (Box 366, Folder 2)
  - 20th Anniversary Dinner-Purchase Orders, 1999 (Box 366, Folder 3)
  - 20th Anniversary Dinner-Photographer, 1999 (Box 366, Folder 4)
  - 20th Anniversary Dinner-Program-Part 1, 1999 (Box 366, Folder 5)
  - 20st Anniversary Dinner-Program-Part 2, 1999 (Box 366, Folder 6)
  - 20th Anniversary Dinner-Centerpieces, March 1, 1999 (Box 366, Folder 7)
  - 20th Anniversary Dinner-Board Dinner-Room and Catering, 1999 (Box 366, Folder 8)
  - 20th Anniversary Dinner-Committee, 1999 (Box 366, Folder 9)
  - C-SPAN Employee Project-Employee On-Air Spots, June-December 1999 (Box 366, Folder 10)
  - C-SPAN Revolution-University of Oklahoma Press, 1999 (Box 366, Folder 11)
  - Marketing/Ads, 1998-1999 (Box 366, Folder 12)
  - Viewer Comments, June 1, 1999 (Box 366, Folder 13)
  - 20th Anniversary Dinner-Correspondence, 1999 (Box 366, Folder 14)
  - House Republican Conference Press Secretary Briefing, March 23, 2007 (Box 367, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN Students and Leaders Folders, circa 2000 (Box 367, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Press Kit, circa 2000 (Box 367, Folder 3)
  - The Common Good Documents, 2000 (Box 367, Folder 4)
  - C-SPAN by the Numbers, circa 2000 (Box 367, Folder 5)
  - 1997 Board Meeting-Attendance/NCTA List/Timeline, June 25, 1997 (Box 367, Folder 6)
  - 1997 Board Meeting-Dinner Arrangments, June 1997 (Box 367, Folder 7)
  - 1997 Board Meeting, June 25, 1997 (Box 367, Folder 8)
  - 1997 Board Elections/New Members, May-June 1997 (Box 367, Folder 9)
  - 1997 Board Meeting-Hotel Accommodations, May 27, 1997 (Box 367, Folder 10)
  - 1997 Board Meeting-Transportation, June 24, 1997 (Box 367, Folder 11)
  - C-SPAN Evening News-Vol. 1, No. 1, June 25, 1997 (Box 367, Folder 12)
  - C-SPAN Evening News Boards, circa 1997 (Box 367, Folder 13)
  - Newseum and Author/Historical Figures Cards, circa 1997 (Box 367, Folder 14)
  - C-SPAN Board of Directors-20 Years Documents, June 23, 1998 (Box 367, Folder 15)
  - C-SPAN Board Ads, 1998 (Box 367, Folder 16)
  - 1998 Board Meeting-Board of Directors Dinner Programs and Name Card, June 23, 1998 (Box 368, Folder 1)
  - 1998 Board Meeting-Decateur House Photos and Correspondence, June 23, 1998 (Box 368, Folder 2)
  - 1998 Board Meeting-Design Cuisine and C-SPAN of Seventeen Documents, March 1996, June 12, 1998 (Box 368, Folder 3)
  - 1998 Board Meeting-Attendance/To-Do List, June 23, 1998 (Box 368, Folder 4)
  - 1998 Board Meeting-Hotel Accommodations (Box 368, Folder 5)
  - 1998 Board Meeting-Board Meeting Business/Structure, April-June 1998 (Box 368, Folder 6)
  - 1998 Board Meeting-Creative, May-June 1998 (Box 368, Folder 7)
  - 1998 Board Meeting-Other Catering, May 1998 (Box 368, Folder 8)
  - 1998 Board Meeting-Board Dinner, March-April 1995, January-June 1998 (Box 368, Folder 9)
  - 1998 Board Meeting-National Cable Television Center and Museum Documents, January-June 1998 (Box 368, Folder 10)
  - 1998 Board Meeting-Board of Directors Agenda, June 23, 1998 (Box 368, Folder 11)
  - 1998 Board Meeting-Board of Directors Agenda and Correspondence-Includes Slides, March 24-25, 1999 (Box 368, Folder 12)
  - Carriage Summaries, March 2000 (Box 368, Folder 13)
  - C-SPAN Executive Committee Agenda, April 10, 2001 (Box 368, Folder 14)
  - C-SPAN Board of Directors Agenda, June 21, 2000 (Box 369, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN Board of Directors Agenda and Documents, September-October 2001 (Box 369, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN Board of Directors Agenda and Documents, November 12, 2002 (Box 369, Folder 3)
  - C-SPAN Executive Committee Conference Call Agenda and Documents, April 5-19, 2002 (Box 369, Folder 4)
  - Board Newsletters, September 1995-February 1996 (Box 369, Folder 5)
  - C-SPAN Board of Directors Meeting and Dinner, May 21-22, 1991 (Box 369, Folder 6)
  - C-SPAN Board of Directors Meeting Documents, May 1991 (Box 369, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors Meeting-To Do, Attendance, and Correspondence, March-May 1991 (Box 370, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors Meeting-Caterer/Lunch, May 1991 (Box 370, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Agenda Cards, May 21-22, 1991 (Box 370, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors Meeting-Radio and Television News Directors Foundation Documents, February 22, 1989-May 1991 (Box 370, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors Meeting-Hotel Accommodations-Capitol Hill Hyatt, March-June 1991 (Box 370, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors Meeting-Transportation, May 14, 1991 (Box 370, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors Meeting-Board Book, April 1990, March 1991 (Box 370, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, May 1991 (Box 370, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors Meeting-Board Dinner, April 9-May 21, 1991 (Box 370, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors Meeting-Printing, May 1991 (Box 370, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors Meeting-Visual Display, December 1990-May 1991 (Box 370, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors Meeting-Cover Letter, May 13, 1991 (Box 370, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Documents and Invitiations, circa May 1991 (Box 370, Folder 13)
  - The National Portrait Gallery Hall of Presidents-C-SPAN Board of Directors Dinner Booklets, 35217 (Box 370, Folder 14)
  - C-SPAN Executive Committee Meeting, 34052 (Box 371, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN Executive Committee Meeting Agenda, 34233 (Box 371, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN Executive Committee Meeting Agenda, 34233 (Box 371, Folder 3)
  - C-SPAN Executive Committee Meeting Documents, 34865 (Box 371, Folder 4)
  - Board Meeting Original Documents, 34486 (Box 371, Folder 5)
  - C-SPAN Board Meeting Documents, 34486 (Box 371, Folder 6)
  - C-SPAN Education Foundation Annual Meeting Agenda, 35345 (Box 371, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN At Seventeen Newsletter, 35125 (Box 371, Folder 8)
  - 1991 Board of Directors Meeting Booklet, circa May 1991 (Box 371, Folder 9)
  - C-SPAN Executive Committee Agenda, February 5, 1997 (Box 372, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN Executive Committee Agenda, February 5, 1997 (Box 372, Folder 2)
  - Original Board of Directors Booklet for Executive Committee Meeting, September 9, 1987 (Box 372, Folder 3)
  - C-SPAN Board of Directors Agenda, June 25, 1997 (Box 372, Folder 4)
  - 1992 Budget Composition Book and Documents, 1991 (Box 372, Folder 5)
  - Budget Presentation-Fiscal Year (FY) 1993, March 10, 1992 (Box 372, Folder 6)
  - Distribution Documents, 1993 (Box 372, Folder 7)
  - FY 1993, circa 1992 (Box 372, Folder 8)
  - FY 1993 Revenue, April 10, 1992 (Box 372, Folder 9)
  - FY 1993, May 8, 1992 (Box 372, Folder 10)
  - FY 1993 Planning-General, 1992 (Box 372, Folder 11)
  - Admin/HR Bonus, March 5, 1992 (Box 372, Folder 12)
  - FY 1993 Budget Planning Composition Book and Documents, 1991-1992 (Box 372, Folder 13)
  - Marketing Documents, January 1992 (Box 372, Folder 14)
  - Finance Documents, 1992-1993 (Box 372, Folder 15)
  - FY 1993-Audio Networks, March 1992 (Box 373, Folder 1)
  - FY 1993-Viewer Services Goals, February-March 1992 (Box 373, Folder 2)
  - FY 1993 Goals, January-March 1992 (Box 373, Folder 3)
  - Master Control Documents, February-March 1992 (Box 373, Folder 4)
  - FY 1993-Programming Department Documents, February 1992-March 1993 (Box 373, Folder 5)
  - Engineering Documents, March 4, 1992 (Box 373, Folder 6)
  - Department of Educational Services FY 1993 Documents, circa 1992 (Box 373, Folder 7)
  - FY 1992 Administration/Human Resources Documents, December 1990-April 1991 (Box 373, Folder 8)
  - FY 1992 Update, 1991 (Box 373, Folder 9)
  - FY 1991, 1990 (Box 373, Folder 10)
  - FY 1992, 1991 (Box 373, Folder 11)
  - FY 1991, April 10, 1991 (Box 373, Folder 12)
  - FY 1992 Budget Analysis, February 12, 1991 (Box 373, Folder 13)
  - FY 1992 Budget Analysis, February 14, 1991 (Box 373, Folder 14)
  - FY 1992 Budget Analysis, February 21, 1991 (Box 373, Folder 15)
  - FY 1992-Revenue Documents, January 24, 1999 (Box 373, Folder 16)
  - Master Control Manager Dave Roycraft Documents, December 1990-February 1991 (Box 373, Folder 17)
  - Audio Networks Documents, March 1991 (Box 373, Folder 18)
  - FY 1992-Finance, 1989-1991 (Box 373, Folder 19)
  - Press Information, February 1991 (Box 373, Folder 20)
  - Engineering Documents-FY 1990-1992, circa 1990-1993 (Box 373, Folder 21)
  - Programming Department Goals, 1990-1991 (Box 373, Folder 22)
  - Viewer Information and Services Department Documents, 1990-1991 (Box 373, Folder 23)
  - Promotions and Publications Documents, 1990-1991 (Box 373, Folder 24)
  - Staff Planning Documents, 1990 (Box 374, Folder 1)
  - Capital Budget Requests, April 9, 1991 (Box 374, Folder 2)
  - Corporate Budget Analysis for Fiscal Year 1992, April 15, 1991 (Box 374, Folder 3)
  - Corporate Goals-FY 1992, September-July 1991 (Box 374, Folder 4)
  - Budget Development and Goals-FY 1992, October-December 1991 (Box 374, Folder 5)
  - Programming Department: 1990 Goals, February 1990 (Box 374, Folder 6)
  - FY 1991 Goals, circa 1990 (Box 374, Folder 7)
  - Finance Department-FY 1991 Goals, 1990 (Box 374, Folder 8)
  - FY 1991 Budget Update, circa 1990 (Box 374, Folder 9)